{
    "id": "d0cb0b3763d342faa2900bdbbc8f8d42",
    "title": "Used To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am not used to ………………….. in cold climates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "living",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "383d1c8e01f742fbb93d15c22c0288e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we were kids, we …………………. go swimming in the evenings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "were used to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3968f18a659b49cc81ab4bc793434dc3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She used to …………………. a lot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "writing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9cf9909c07ac4331a5d5633511a9418a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not used to ………………….. on the left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drive",
                "driving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7fa082d81634312b75639003d5a1df6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t use to ………………….. fish or meat, but now I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eat",
                "eating"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb6cfbdd80ce461592c85d17d0143857"
        },
        {
            "question": "He quit his job in Saudi Arabia because he ………………… .. living in such a hot country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was not used to",
                "did not used to",
                "did not use to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d3772698ba64fc6aad95755ab6808a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are used to ………………….. in poverty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19a71e92506e4d49923aa7667ad9c284"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will soon get used to ………………….. things on your own.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "doing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a860e0783d8b4474b2f672156c5b5754"
        },
        {
            "question": "First-time mothers often find it difficult to get used to ………………….. up in the middle of the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f40adfcc353341aebe6ddfcf5b480466"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… to like him, but now I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used not",
                "didn't use",
                "use to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4737bda8305446f99b802377de39df46"
        }
    ]
}